I'm not saying I'll quit after all...
やっぱりやめますとかって言わないけど...
There isn't.
ないよ
...
It's better to help someone other than your husband like this...
旦 那さん以外とこうやって手伝うとできるより...
If you help someone other than your husband like this, you can do it like this...
旦那さん以外とこうやって手伝うとできるよりこうやって...
About 3 people?
3人出るくらい?
3 people
3人
...
Ya, this is it...
や だよな、これ...
Are you popular?
モテるよね?
Yeah ...
うん ...
close?
近い?
You have a beautiful face
綺麗な顔してる
Right?
よね?
Is it your second year of marriage?
結 婚生活2年目だっけ?
yes...
はい...
It's my first time to feel so excited...
初めてだよ、こういうわくわきっていうか...
When I started filming, I too...
撮影始めたら俺も...
Will you become husband and wife?
結婚夫妻にする?
Don't you know?
知らないっすか?
Yes, just a moment...
はい、ちょっと...
If things get bad...
悪いようになったら...
Is that so?
そうなの?
Can I be your wife?
奥さんでいい?
yes...
はい...
Is it your full time job?
専業なの?
Full time job?
専業?
Full-time housewife?
専業主婦?
I'm a full-time housewife
専業主婦です
...
You're doing something wrong right now...
い けないことしてるね、今...
Are you from far away?
遠く出身なの?
yes...
はい...
Because my teeth are beautiful...
歯が綺麗だから...
Small and cute...
小ぶりで可愛い...
Should I leave this there?
これ、そっち置いとく?
Okay...
いいよ...
Are you worried?
心配でしょ?
It's so red, I agree...
すごい赤いね、同感だよね...
Even though I say high school students, high school students might also be good...
高校生って言っても 高校生もいいかもしれない...
Well said...
よく言われました...
I'm surprised that it became one...
1つになってびっくりだよね...
I'm tired...
くすがった...
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Embarrassing...
恥ずかしい...
thin
細い
...
身 長100?
How many centimeters?
何センチだろう?
It's very long
めっちゃ長いです
...
Will it hurt?
痛 いするのかな?
Can I give you a break?
勘弁していい?
I'll give you a break, okay?
勘弁しちゃうよ?
Isn't it embarrassing?
恥ずかしいでしょ?
I'm sleeping...
寝れてる...
I'm sleeping
寝れてる
...
How long have you been away?
ど れくらいしてないの?
About half a year...
半年くらい...
If you don't do that...
そんなしないと...
It's so wet...
ビチャビチャだね...
Still small...
まだ小さい...
It's small.
小さいね
...
Are you embarrassed?
恥 ずかしい?
It's so wet
ビチャビチャだね
...
Glitris face...
グ リトリスの顔...
Someone there too...
そこにも誰か...
I went out...
出かかりました...
Have you observed it yourself?
自分で観察したことある?
Either way, open it and show me what's inside.
どっちで中見せて開いて
...
What if your husband saw this?
これ、 旦那さん見たらどう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's open
開いてて
...
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Embarrassment will win
恥ずかしさが勝っちゃうね
...
綺 麗...
I want to go to bed and drink a lot...
ちょっとベッド行って、いっぱい飲みたくなって...
amazing...
すごい...
This is amazing...
すごいこれ...
This is amazing
これすごい
...
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Yeah ...
うん ...
this side
こっち側
...
Try moving your hands...
手 動かしてみて...
How far will you go?
どこまで行くの?
to this point?
ここまで?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Are you thinking of going?
行っちゃいそう?
I feel like my body is full of fat...
体がベタばかりみたい...
Very narrow...
すごい狭い...
This side...
こっち側...
Is it meaningful?
意味深い?
feet...
足...
Have you never had this kind of sex?
このセックスしたことない?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Husband, I just dredged...
旦那さん、今ドレッジしちゃったけど...
Is it the worst?
最悪か?
I was wrong, right?
間違ったでしょ?